live like said welcome brothers and
sisters to another Wednesday question
and answer will we open up with the Ten
Commandments that God commanded the
whole world to keep brother
tanzel and God spake all these words
saying I am the Lord thy God which have
brought thee out of the land of Egypt
out of the house of bondage I have no
other gods before me thou shall not make
unto thee any Graven image or any
likeness of anything that is in heaven
above or that is in the earth beneath or
that is in the water under the Earth
thou shall not bow down thyself to them
nor serve them why the Lord thy God I'm
a jealous God visiting the iniquities of
the fathers upon the children unto the
third and fourth generation of them that
hate me and showing Mercy unto thousands
of them that love me and keep my
Commandments thou shall not take the
name of the Lord thy God in vain for the
Lord will not hold him guil that take of
his name in vain remember the Sabbath
day to keep it holy six days shall thou
labor and do all thy work but the
seventh day is the Sabbath of the Lord
thy God and it thou shall not do any
work thou nor thy son nor thy daughter
thy man servant nor thy maid servant nor
thy cattle nor thy stranger that is
within thy gates for in six days the
Lord made Heaven and Earth the sea and
all that in them is and rested the
seventh day wherefore the Lord blessed
the Sabbath day and hollowed it honor
thy father and thy mother that the days
may be long upon the land which the Lord
thy God give thee thou shall not kill
thou shall not commit adultery thou
shall not steal thou shall not bear
false witness against thy neighbor thou
not cover thy neighbor's house thou not
cover thy neighbor's wife nor his man's
servant nor his made servant no his Ox
nor his ass nor anything that is thy
neighbors we read Exodus 21-1 17 may the
Lord have a blessing to the reading of
his word in Jesus name we pray amen
amen so here on question and answer you
can ask us a question and we'll answer
it according to the King James Bible and
if we cannot find the answer we will
seek further counsel to bring you an
answer at a later time and these are the
questions that we will not answer the
vague and long scripture questions and
the questions of debate we will not
answer those questions we are here to
spread the true Gospel of
God so please be as direct as possible
with your answers so we can be as direct
as possible with our answers out of the
King James Bible nor the Bibles or books
will be an knowledge on this program
this is a live stream so feel free to
send in your questions that pertain to
everlasting life we just ask that you
keep your question to a two scripture
maximum let me introduce to you the
family that's on the panel this evening
brother Dre good evening brother Jerome
Grace and peace Brother Julius good
evening everybody brother tanzel good
evening sister Deborah good
evening and we and we have sister Casey
and the guest caller with us and I'm
brother Cornell sister Deborah what is
our first question of the evening yes
there are several held over questions
that will be answered first before
getting into tonight's Q&A Toria Davis
asks when the abomination of desolation
is sitting in the Holy place are we're
supposed to immediately flee to the
mountains or go home until we are led by
a
messenger then be taken to the
Wilderness all right so talking about
the abomination of desolation guess
called well if you go into Matthew the
24th chapter it tell you when you
therefore shall see the abomination of
desolation standing in the Holy Place
whoo read it understand man then flee to
the mountains so now you don't wait on
nobody what you do is you look around
for the transportation that God will
have because if you're going to wait you
mess around and get
caught no you don't wait on no messenger
that's all I have to say all right hope
that answered your question as we
continue to move to our next question
next question Valencia as are we who no
who are the scribes and Pharisees are
they
Romans who are the scribes and Pharisees
brother
Julius no they're not Romans Romans are
Gentiles the scribes and Pharisees were
the religious teachers and writers and
uh uh of uh uh in Jesus time and even
before Jesus time they were all uh
Israelites they were all Israelites
sisters and brothers so the Pharisees
were the one with the teachers and the
uh upholders and enforcers of the law
and the scribes were the writers let me
give you uh a couple of uh famous let's
go to Ezra chapter
7 so you a scribe is a a writer he take
dictations he uh somebody is telling
them what to write and they wrote they
copied out the documents onto scroll
that's what the scribes did Ezra 7 and
verse 6 Ezra 7 and verse 6 go ahead
tenzel this Ezra went up from Babylon
and he was ready scribe in the law of
Moses which the L which the Lord God of
Israel had given and the King graned him
all his requests according to the hand
of the Lord and his God upon him so he
was a ready scribe he was a writer not
only but he was more a little bit more
than that Ezra multitasking but he was
already scribe a writer now let's go to
Acts cause Jeremiah had a scribe Baro
you on your own you can read about that
he had his scribe Jeremiah uh and let's
look at Acts 26 and let's look at
another
Pharisee Acts chapter 26 and when you
get it my brother we gonna read verse
one and skip Acts chapter
26 and read verse
one then a grippa said unto Paul Thou
Art permitted to speak for thyself then
Paul stretched forth the hand and
answered for himself verse
four my manner of life from my youth
which was at the first among my own
Nations at Jerusalem know all the Jews
continue which knew me from the
beginning and they would testify that
after the most straightest SE of our
religion I lived the Pharisee so Paul
was a phese and Paul was of The Tribe of
Benjamin sisters and brothers so Paul
was a teacher and upholder of the
law which was the Commandments of God
the statutes and the Commandments of God
so no they were not Romans no they were
Israelites the the teachers and the
upholders of the law and the scribes
were their writers that's all I got yes
sir brother Julius you only have I known
out all the families of the Earth right
that's right that's right all right
thank you for that brother hope that
answered their question as we move on to
our next moving on Tama Co asks if a gay
person enters the congregation would we
deal with that what how would we deal
with that do we welcome them or turn the
back all right brother Jerome what you
say well the Lord don't want any of us
to perish he want us to
turn and and live so they they should
have an opportunity
to turn and we give them opportunity so
they can get this word understand this
word so that they can learn that the
Lord not pleased with that lifestyle and
if they can turn they can save from this
UNT generation okay so we should give
him that opportunity to do that now all
right uh because the Lord did that for
us but let's go to uh Ezekiel chapter
18 and read verse 23 and then we gonna
skip have I any pleasure at all that the
wicked should die sayeth the Lord God
and not that he should return from his
ways and live skip down to verse 27 and
read it to
32 again when the Wicked Man turth away
from his wickedness that he have
committed and doth that which is lawful
and right he shall save his soul
alive because he consider and turn away
from all his transgression that he ha
committed he shall surely live he shall
not
die yet sayth the house of Israel the
way of the Lord is not equal oh House of
Israel are not my ways equal are not
your ways unequal skip down to verse 31
read to 32 cast away from you all your
transgression whereby ye have
transgressed it and make you a new heart
and a new spirit for why will ye die oh
House of Israel for I have no pleasure
in the death of them that dieth sayeth
the Lord God wherefore turn yourselves
and
live that's all I got on me
all right hope that answers your
question as we continue to move on to
our next yes uh moving on this is one of
our most popular question uh questions
uh Kathy Mills says can we use
microwaves to heat food and coffee pots
on the
Sabbath no and no no microwave and no
coffee pots to heat on the Sabbath the
Sabbath is a day with that you are
supposed to plan for it so let's go into
Exodus 16 Exodus the 16th
chapter and let's see how the Lord had
it set up when he had food being brought
in and he had it brought in before the
Sabbath day let's see how it was handled
Exodus 16 and pick it up at verse
22 and came to pass that on the sixth
day they gather twice as much bread to
omers of one man for all the rulers of
the congregation came and told
Moses and he said unto him this is that
which the Lord ha said tomorrow is the
rest of a holy Sabbath unto the Lord so
bake that which ye will bake today and
see it that ye will see it and that
which remain if overlay up for you to be
kept until the morning so Lord had it
here with that on on the sixth day which
is the day before the Sabbath day you
gather twice as much so you don't have
to do no laboring work on that seventh
day you already have your food already
together and prepared because this day
the Sabbath day is Holy unto the Lord
and we should do all we can to please
him go
ahead and they laid it up till the
morning as Moses B and it did not stink
neither was there any worms
therein and Moses said eat that today
for today is a Sabbath unto the Lord and
today ye shall not find it in the fields
uhhuh six days He Shall Gather it but on
the seven day which is the Sabbath in it
there shall be none so the food that you
gathered on the sixth day hey on the
Sabbath day there's going to be none
because you supposed to be straight you
planed ahead and you did your bakon on
the sixth day and your boiling and all
that stuff verse
27 and it came to pass that there went
out some of the people in the seventh
day for The Gather and they found none
and the Lord got upset about that go
ahead and the Lord said unto Moses for
how long refuse ye to keep my
Commandments and my
laws see for that the Lord hath given
you the Sabbath therefore he giveth you
on the sixth day the bread of two
days abide ye every man in his place let
no man go out of his place on the
seventh day
uhhuh so the people rested on the
seventh day so Lord is saying here that
hey I gave you enough to supply you for
the Sabbath day I just wanted you to
plan and put everything together on
Friday so that Saturday you will be
straight so you have a way of being able
to prepare your meals without having to
use the microwave and the coffee pot and
get yourself in trouble with the Lord
turn over quickly to Isaiah 56 and we're
going to read two verses Isaiah 56
because the Lord is well pleased when we
plan and do it according to the way he
said do it Isaiah 56 and read 1 and
two thus sayeth the Lord keep ye
judgment and do justice for my salvation
is near to come and my righteousness to
be
revealed well bless is the man that
doeth this and the son of man that layth
hold on it that keepeth the Sabbath from
polluting it and keepeth his hand from
doing any evil so you bring blessings
upon yourself when you keep the Sabbath
day the way the Lord say do it and uh
not doing it according to the way you
might think with the microwave or the
coffee pot plant ah head and the Lord
will be well pleased that's all I
got and we hope that answered your
question as we move on to our
next next question Terence mckenny Jr
asked
why did Peter baptize Gentiles without
getting
circumcised and he gives acts 10 vers
44-48 Dre what you
say I say tance that he did not baptize
Gentiles uncircumcised the book don't
say that you can't read that in there
but let's just go read acts 10 and start
at verse 44
acts 10 starting at verse 44 go ahead
while Peter yet spake these words the
Holy Ghost fell on all of them which
heard the
word and they of the circumcision which
believ were astonished as many as came
with Peter because on the Gentiles also
was poured out the gift of the Holy
Ghost for they heard them speak with
tongue to magnify God then answered
Peter can any man forbid War order that
these should not be baptized which have
received the Holy Ghost as well as
we and he commanded them to be baptized
in the name of the Lord then prayed they
him to T certain days now you don't read
nowhere in there that they were
uncircumcised in fact we we dealt with
this question last week and I will
encourage you to go back to last week we
spent we spent 13
minutes and 15 seconds dealing with all
of this in
detail and it's at the 31 minute and 30
second Mark to the 44th minute and 45
second
mark
look this talked about devout man if you
bag up bag up read verse one and
two go ahead brother there was a certain
man in caser called Cornelius a
centurion of the band called The Italian
band a devout man and one that feared
God with all his house which gave much
arms to the people and prayed to God
always now we talking about a devout man
that feared God in all his
house which gave arms and they prayed to
God always and an
angel came and told him to go seek Peter
and he will tell tell you what you must
do right now I I again I would encourage
you to go back to last week and look at
that answer and it will give you all the
detail you want it did not say that they
were
uncircumcised or they were circumcised
that's nowhere in there that is an
assumption on your part don't assume
read what it said man that's all I got
yes sir brother Dre that is true hey if
Abraham did it at 99 so goes everybody
else right that's
right all right thank you for that
brother hope that answered your question
as we move on to our next moving on
Deborah
walers ask for you to explain Zechariah
4:
10-14 Zechariah
41-14 brother Julius
let's go there uh let's
go Zechariah the 4th
chapter you have to start it from the
beginning but we're not going to start
from the beginning but uh as a summary
you have to begin uh and understand the
Lord sent an
angel to Zachariah and it's a vision of
the
future we're gonna show you this since
in the future because the Bible dates
itself Zechariah
four and pick it up at verse
uh 10 read that
scripture for who have despised the day
of small things uhhuh they shall rejoice
and shall see the plummet in the land of
zerubabel those in the hand in the hand
of zerubabel
yes they are the eyes of the Lord which
run to and fro through the whole earth
yes then answered I and said unto him
for what are these two olive trees upon
right side of the Candlestick and upon
the left side
thereof and I answered again and said
unto him what be these two Olive
branches with that which Dre two golden
pipes empty the golden ore out of
themselves uhhuh and he answered me and
said knowest thou not what these be and
I said no my Lord then said he these are
the two anointed ones that stand by the
lord of the whole earth so now this
whole scripture this whole chapter uh is
a continuation of the previous chapter
but it's showing you in the throne room
of the Lord the instruments the
Candlestick if you read verse one it'll
tell you that the angel that talk with
me and wake me as a man waking out of
his sleep and he said ask him what do
you see Zachariah so he's showing
Zachariah the future so now then he
mentions the hands of zerubabel
zerubabel is dead and in the ground but
when the Lord return he going to be at
the first resurrection he going he going
to be a spirit beard we're talking
future here then the seven at verse 10
is the seven angels that he got th to
and fr in the earth now let's look at
these two olive trees and who are they
let's go to Revelation the 11th chapter
now we going to go into our day and time
now and this is what we're waiting to
see because we in the end time
Revelation
11 and pick it up at verse one in
Revelation 11 and one and then we'll
skip it dates itself go
ahead and there was given me a read like
unto a and the angels stood saying rise
and measure the temple of God and God at
it's not here but now he sure he when it
comes this is what's going to uh this is
who going to be a going to build this
Temple him and some more Immortals go
ahead and the Altar and them that
worship therein yes but but the court
which is without the temple leave out
and measure it not for it is given unto
the Gentiles and the holy city shall
they tread Under Foot 40 and two months
that is the duration of the Great
Tribulation period 42 months 1,260 days
time times in a dividing of time this is
under the hand of West in Europe This is
a they're going to Trad down the holy
city when they put pop up in there it's
going to start a Great Tribulation now
what about these two witnesses who are
they verse three and I will give power
unto my two witnesses and they shall
prophesy the th23 score days cloth and
sackcloth so while the Great Tribulation
is going on the Lord gonna have his two
witnesses preaching the gospel you know
and verse four go ahead these are the
two olive trees and the two candlesticks
standing before the god of the earth so
now we didn't read in Zechariah the
fourth chapter but the two the
candlesticks are there everything is
there so now these are these two arive
trees or these two branches these are
the two witnesses that the Lord is going
to use to offset the uh Satan's Minister
doing a Great Tribulation sisters and
brothers so the the Zachariah dates so
he's sh the angel is showing Zechariah
the vision of the future in our day and
time I hope that
helps all right brother that's good
light on what's yet to come and those
two witnesses are not Moses and Elijah
no all right hope that answered your
question as we move on to our next uh
next one be alert have two questions one
pleas please explain what Apostle Paul
meant in Acts 19
verse2 and number two is the gift of
Holy Ghost the word of God from his
angels all right Jerome share some light
let's go read it acts 19 verse
two Acts
19 verse two
and he said unto them have ye received
the Holy Ghost since ye believe and they
said unto him we have not so much as
heard whether there being Holy Ghost any
Holy Ghost yeah so understand that you
know God sends his he sends his holy
word and he uses his holy angels to lead
and guide us into all truth and he said
my word is
truth okay so let's go to
um St John chapter
14 and pick it up at the 15 Read to the
16 we G to
skip if you love me keep my
Commandments
16 and I will pray the father and he
shall give you another confident that he
may abide with you forever okay he said
he that that he referring to is called
the comforter he's also called the
spirit of Truth skip down to verse
26 but the comforter which is the Holy
Ghost whom the father will send in my
name he shall teach you all things and
bring all things to your Rememberance
whatsoever I have said unto you that's
the job of this Holy Ghost this the
spirit of truth that referred to as a he
here he's an angel okay and he going to
lead and guide you into all truth the
word of God okay um go to the uh 16th
chapter and read verse 13 through 15
then we're gonna go to Revelations after
that how be it when he the spirit of
truth is if is come he will guide you
unto all truth he shall not speak of
himself but whatsoever he shall hear
that shall he speak and he will show you
things to come uhuh he shall glorify me
for he shall receive of mine and shall
show it unto
you all things that the father have are
mine so therefore said I that he shall
take of mine and shall show it unto
you that's go to Revelations 1 we going
to read verse 1 and
two go ahead the revelation of Jesus
Christ which God gave un to him to show
unto his servants things which must
shortly come to pass and he sent and
signified it by his angels unto his
servant John yeah that's how that's
that's the protocol that's how how it
work Revelations 22 verse 16 that'll be
it read verse
two uh now you can go to Revelations uh
22 and read verse
16 I Jesus have sent my angels to
testify unto you these things in the
churches I am the root and The Offspring
of David and the bright and Morning Star
yeah so he used this Holy Angel to give
you the holy word and and that Holy
Angel is the Holy Ghost and he gonna
lead and guide you the all
truth that's all I got
on all right thank you for that brother
hope that answered that question next
question please next question Stephen
Gus asked in Genesis 11: 4 and 5 does
this Tower represents Jesus and what
about the tower in Isaiah 5 verse2 do
these two towers represent
Jesus all right why we go to Genesis
11 and they ask about scripture four and
five asking does this Tower represent
Jesus and the guest called would take it
from
there Genesis 114 and 5 and they said go
to let us build us a city and a tower
whose top May reach unto heaven and let
us make us a name lest we be scattered
abroad upon the face of the old Earth
and the Lord came down to see the city
and the tower which the children of men
built look there was actually a tower
and a
city and to show you that it couldn't be
Jesus he's the one that come down and
Confused it so skip down to verse let's
let's read verses uh uh
uh
4 through
n pick it up at four and read through n
Go ahead and they said go to let us
build us a city in the to power whose
top May reach unto heaven and let us
make us a name L we be scattered abroad
upon the face of the whole earth and the
Lord came down to see the city and the
tower which the children of men built it
and the Lord said behold the people is
one and they have all one language and
this they begin to do and now nothing
will be restrained from them which they
have imagined to do so go to let us go
down and there confound their language
that they may not understand one
another's speech so the Lord scattered
them abroad from then upon the face of
all the Earth and they left off to build
the city therefore is the name of it
called Babel because the Lord did there
confound the language of all the Earth
and from this did the Lord scatter them
abroad upon the face of all the
Earth it was actually a tower they
thought they could build a tower to
heaven and reason was no matter how they
spread out they could look back to the
Tower and go back to the origin it was
actually a
tower that's why the book said they left
off building they stopped
building that's
correct and the other uh scripture given
is Isaiah 5 verse two is this Tower
talking about Jesus Isaiah 5 verse
two no it's not talking about Jesus
either that's a metaphor that the Lord
give to let you know that he gave
Israel everything they
needed yep and
uh they broke all his laws and statutes
let's go into Isaiah the 5th chapter
read verses
4-7 because he said you know uh uh when
he look for grapes there was wild grapes
this is told talking about Israel and
his
law 5
4-7 what could have been done more to my
Vineyard that I have not done in it
wellfor when I look that it should bring
forth grapes brought it forth wild
grapes and now go to I will tell you
what I will do to my Vineyard I will
take away the head thereof and it shall
be eaten up and Break Down The Walls
thereof and it shall be trien down and I
will lay it waste it shall not be pruned
nor dig but there shall come up briers
and thorns and I will also command the
clouds that they rain no rain upon it
for the vineyard of the Lord of hosts is
the house of Israel and the men of Judah
his Pleasant plant and he look for
judgment but behold oppression or
righteousness but Behold a
cry so that's just a metaphor they use a
Vineyard in the tower it's just like
what was necessary to have a good uh uh
uh Vineyard where they made wine and
stuff and like you would put everything
in it that you need to make a good
product so he was using that to let him
know let us know that he gave Israel
good laws and statutes that we should
live by so we said when he look for
grapes he found Wild grapes that mean
when he look for righteousness he found
oppression and he found sin so neither
one of them represent
Jesus all I have to say right hope that
anwers your question is we move on to
our next question with a Time Check Yes
the time is uh
802 nor is tape
as what happened to Jesus spiritual body
when he took took over the body he had
prepared in Mary's womb being that
Spirits can't
die what happened to Jes right I'm
curious okay so what happened to Jesus
Spirit body when he was planted in
Mary's womb guess
caller let tell you something I can't
find nothing written in the book you
tell me
anything uh on the order of this
question so being that is not
written we can't ask the question that's
one you sa and ask the Lord when you get
there because it is written the secret
things belong to the
Lord that's all I have to say all
right hope that answered your question
next
question next question D law says can
iog please
consider vetting the books of Enoch it's
aligned with the Holy Bible please
research all right it's uh it's not fair
that you even presented this question
because we speak in the beginning of the
program that we deal with the King James
Bible only but let's open it up to the
panel for further
discussion well
look when people always talking about
certain books
they should go and B them and read them
no this cannot be
a uh a part of the Bible because the
Book of Enoch first thing it was written
by a
gentile Joseph B
lampkins the second thing is you don't
have no Nephilim in the
Bible and the Book of Enoch quotes a few
things out of the Bible then they go on
and they have their own story I bought
the book I read the book so the person
that asked this question tell me that
you have not read the book have you
going to say that it coincide with the
Bible that's all I have to say so
no we can't use
that all right as we continue to move on
to our next question next question and
Tom Riley says my kids play sports and
the games are on the Sabbath day what
shall I
do well if those Sports aren't required
for your child to pass his classes to
graduate in school then you should be
putting the Lord's Sabbath Day first
always so let's go and let's read let's
go to Deuteronomy the 6th chapter
Deuteronomy the 6th chapter
because it's very important that you
teach your children the correct way that
they should go because if not you leave
the door open for them to turn around
and teach their children that it's
okay let's go Deuteronomy the 6th
chapter and let's read verse one and
two now these are the Commandments the
statutes and the Judgment which the Lord
your God commanded to teach you that ye
might do them in the in the land whether
you go to possess
it that thou mayest fear the lord thy
God to keep all his statutes and his
Commandments which I command thee thou
and thy son and thy son Sons all the
days of thy life and thy days may be
prolonged so the Lord is saying that
this is all supposed to be passed down
not only from the the grandparents down
to the parents and then to the children
also skip down to verse five and go
ahead and thou shalt love the Lord thy
God with all thy heart and with all thy
soul and with all thy
might and these words which I command
thee this day shall be in thy
heart and thou sht teach them diligently
unto thy children and shall take and
should talk of them when thou sest in
thine house and when thou west by the
way and when thou thou liest down and
when thou Rises up yeah because we have
to always keep the Lord's Sabbath Day
first it is a day that he rests and he
set it aside for us to rest also and he
got requirements and so if it's not
great related as far as your kids
playing sports they should be honoring
the Sabbath just like everybody else so
that you can teach your children the way
to honor the Sabbath so that they don't
turn around and think it's so okay for
them to do the same for their children
so that's all I got on
that and we hope that that answered your
question as we continue to move on to
our next moving on Tracy burges asked
what is the correct way to
fast so Dre when you want to fast what's
the correct way
brother uh let's go to uh Daniel the
10th chapter Daniel
10 and pick it up at verse two when you
get there read that
brother in those days I D was morning
three four
weeks I ate no Pleasant bread neither
came flesh nor wine in my mouth neither
did I anoint myself at all till three
whole weeks were fulfilled so d here he
didn't eat no bread
no the bread is described as pleasant
but he said he ate no bread neither
flesh came into his mouth nor
wine and he did not anoint himself he
did that for three weeks now let's go
look at some something else let's go to
Esther the fourth chapter Esther
4 Esther 4 and I want to pick it up at
verse uh verse
16 no verse 15 Read verse
15 then Esther B them returned Mori this
answer so Esther gave an answer for Mori
to do something because hmon wanted to
kill all the Israelites and and uh Mori
came
and let Esther know what was going on so
Esther gave Mori this to do go ahead
verse
16 go gather together all the Jews that
are present in Chuan and fast ye for me
and neither eat nor drink three days
night or
day I also and my maidens will Fast
likewise and so will I go in unto the
King which is not according to the law
and if I perish I perish I notice here
it says fast ye for me and neither eat
nor drink three days so a fast is when
you're not eating nor
drinking now let's go to uh let's go to
um let's go to Matthew
6 I want to touch on this real quick
Matthew 6 and read verse 16-
18 go ahead
brother moreover when ye fast be not as
the Hypocrites of a sad continence for
they disfigure their FA that they may
appear unto men to fast but I say unto
you they have their
reward but thou when thou fastest anoint
thy head and wash thy face that thou
appear not unto men to fast but unto thy
father which is in secret and thy father
which seeth in secret shall reward thee
open yeah because so this is what a fast
is about a fast is about you're not
eating and you're not drinking right you
know I'm just not gonna eat donuts this
week I'm fasting on Donuts no it's when
you're not eating nor drinking right
that
help all right thank you for that
brother as we move on to our next
question next question June green
says on a Sabbath night Friday and
Sabbath morning Saturday am I allowed to
give my husband a kiss in Isaiah
58 verse 13 is given all right you wake
up on the Sabbath day can you give your
husband a kiss brother Dre let's go read
that Isaiah 58
and13 read that when you get it
brother if thou turn away thy foot from
the Sabbath from doing thy pleasure on
my holy day and call the Sabbath of
delight the holy of the Lord honorable
and shall honor him not doing their own
ways nor finding their own pleasure nor
speaking thy own words so yeah you know
you can kiss your husband but you should
not have some type of passionate kiss
like you getting ready to make love to
your husband or something on the Sabbath
day that would be your pleasure right
okay but let's look at it at a kiss here
let's go to uh first Thessalonians
5 1 Thessalonians
5 and read verse 22 and we gonna skip
Iain first Thessalonians
5 abstain from all appearances of
evil skip down to verse
26 greet all the Brethren with a holy
kiss so if you can greet the Brethren
with a holy kiss you can certainly greet
your husband with a holy kiss but it
don't have to be a passionate one it can
be one
of love just like you would your
brothers or your sisters let's go to
First Peter the 5th chapter and we just
gonna read verse 14 and that'll be it
first Peter 5 and
14 go ahead and read it when you get it
brother greet ye one another with a kiss
of
Charity peace be with you all that are
in Christ Jesus amen so hey it ain't
nothing wrong with you giving your
husband a kiss but if you kissing your
husband like y'all trying to go
somewhere else maybe you should wait
until after the Sabbath to do that
right that's all I
got all right thank you for that brother
as we move on to our next
question uh yes we are now into
tonight's Q&A for Wednesday December
the 11
2024 and uh all day production have two
questions one habaka 2 verse 15 what is
this nakedness talking about here and
two Job 1 verse
6 is this in the third heaven where
these angels meet with the
Lord all right so why don't we go to
that habaka 2
and5 when you get there tanzel go ahead
and the guest caller will take it from
therea is hiding me two and 15 Bak is
going to be um you got Micah nahon then
you got habaka right before the book
zephani habaka 2
and5 yes woe unto him that giveth his
neighbor drink that putteth thy bottle
to him that maketh him drunken also that
thou mayest look on their
nakedness so the question is what is
this nakedness talking about
here you know
it could actually be talking about
nakedness like taking your clothes off
it's really talking about taking
advantage of
somebody you know like uh you can get
them drunk and you can uh do things it's
just like a bunch of evil people that
want to to persuade a king to do
something let's go into
hose 7th
chapter read verse one and Skip down to
verse five
read it when you get there when I will
have healed Israel then the iniquity of
Ephraim was discovered and the
wickedness of Samaria for they committed
falsehood and the thief cometh in and
the troops of robbers spoed
without so now these a bunch of e Israel
were doing a bunch of evil stuff they
wanted to get away with it so skip down
to verse five what did they do
concerning the ruler go ahead
in the day of our King the princes have
made him sick with bottles of wine he
stretched out his hand with
scorners so now what they do made him
sick with a bottle of wine like what get
him drunk now he go along with evil
people it was just telling you could
actually be this is talking about a a
physical drunk we not talking about
religion drunk
here so you get a person that's drunk
you can do anything while they're drunk
just like uh uh uh Noah got drunk and he
got
naked that's all I have to
say all right and the and the other
question uh from uh all day production
in Job 1 verse 6 is this in the third
heaven where these angels meet with the
Lord Job 1 verse six go
read now there was a day when the sons
of God came to present themselves before
the Lord and Satan came also among
them now Satan is an angel and these
sons of God in this case are angels and
to come before the Lord you don't have
to be in the third heaven because Satan
cannot go back to the third heaven cuz
he was thrown out of it right so now
whether the meeting with the other sons
of God was in heaven I don't know and
nobody else know but the only thing I
know for sure that Satan wasn't in the
third heaven but then why is it on this
Earth that you can go that you do not be
in the presence of God God know you
wherever you are let's go and look at
what G Cain said in Genesis the 4th
chapter we're going to read 13 uh uh
Genesis 4:13 and
14 Genesis 4:13 to
14 and Cain said unto the
Lord my punishment is greater than I can
bear and behold thou H has driven me out
this day from the face of the Earth and
from thy face shall I be hid and I shall
be a fugitive and a vagabond and the
Earth and it shall come to pass that
everyone that fth me shall slay
me so now Cain never went to heaven so
when he said and th face from thy face
I'm going be he in other words he was
the God saw him whever he
was so now wherever you are don't make
no difference whether these uh sons of
God was in the third heaven I don't know
whether it was on the earth I don't know
but what I do know is that Satan cannot
go through the third heaven so it's most
likely that's these five these spirits
of God these seven Eyes Of God that run
two and fr in Earth they probably Angels
that's all over this Earth and they have
to report they can go to heaven if they
want to but Satan can't that's all I
have to say all right hope that answered
your question as we move on to our next
one I'm moving on TX Domino needs some
clarity
verification
uh they state in St John 1
verse3 we read that Jesus the son the
word made everything and not the father
but in proverbs 30 verse4 at the end of
the verse it reads what is his name and
what is his son's name now TX Domino
States this is saying the father made it
all if I'm correct shouldn't that verse
say what is his father's name because
Jesus the son has ascended and descended
not the
father right so why don't we go to John
1 and verse three and verse
three and the question in regards to
that John 1 and3 is what Deborah he is
presenting uh a statement saying that in
John 1 verse3 it does says that Jesus
the son the word made everything and not
the father but then he says well I need
some clarification because in Proverbs
three uh proverbs 30
verse4 at the end of that verse it reads
what is his name and what is his son's
name and he States TX Domino
says this is saying the father made it
all now that's his
statement and then so he needs some
clarification on this all right well
there is definitely some light for that
let's go to John 1 and three and the
guest caller will take it from there
John 1 and verse three
all things were made by him and without
him was not anything made that was
made well they let you know that with
Jesus actually his hand is the one that
did to make
it but
now go in uh 30th
chapter a proverb and read
it who have ascended up into heaven or
descended who who have gathered the
winds in his fist who have bound the
waters in the
Garment who have established all the
ends of the Earth what is his name and
what is his son's name if thou can
tell but the first thing is just because
Jesus did all of that there's nothing
that say that the father didn't do that
also now let's go and you say what is
his name and what's his son's name let's
go into St
John 5th
chapter and we're going to read verse
43 I am come in my father's name and ye
receive me not and if another shall come
in his own name him ye will
receive so now first thing is what his
name his name is Jesus cuz that was the
father's name and Jesus came in his
father's
name but the whole thing
is the only time the book say and that's
in also in uh St John 5 and 37 that no
man have seen the father at any time or
heard seen his sheap any time heard his
voice so now I
I
built my
house but I didn't lay one
brick I didn't nail One
Nail but I built it huh because I'm the
one that gave the orders to do it but
Jesus told you he do only what his
father say
yeah beyond that I don't have nothing
else to say can we read um um Ephesians
the 3r chapter verse 99 it's going to
say exactly what guest caller just
said 3 and9 yes
sir and to make all men see what is the
Fellowship of the
mystery which from the beginning of the
world have been hid in God who created
All Things by Jesus Christ there you
go that's
it just like you build a house you don't
one brick you don't nail One Nail but
you built it CU you're the one that gave
the
order and the one that did it he built
it also because he did the physical
work I said it's all
have all right thank you for that add on
hope that answered that question as we
move
on move on sister Tanisha asked if
someone put flowers on a grave and come
into your house does that make you
unclean even if you didn't touch them
what about your house is your house
unclean because they came in your home
if so how long is your home and or you
unclean all right let's go to uh numbers
19 let's read a couple of verses and
then open it up to the p
numbers
19 pick it up at that verse read 14- 16
and then we'll open it up to the P go
ahead brother this is the law when a man
dieth in a tent all that come into the
tent and all that is in the tent shall
be unclean seven
days and every open vessel which have no
covering bound upon it is
unclean and whosoever touches one that
is slain with the sword in the open
feeli or dead body or bone of a man or
gray she'll be unclean seven
days all right open to the panel the
question again
der the question is they want to
know um how long if your home and or you
are
unclean can you read that um skip down
to the 22nd verse to in that same
chapter numbers 19 Verse
22 and whatsoever the unclean person
toucheth shall be unclean and the soul
that toucheth it shall be unclean until
even you know I'm looking at this
question and I'm reminded when Israel
was in their land the Lord said when you
go to relieve yourself carry a weap a
paddle on on your weapon and and and
turn around when you go to relieve
yourself turn around and bury that was
coming from you that the Lord see no
unclean thing they didn't have indoor
washrooms they had their they had places
outside the camp where they would go and
relieve themselves I have a washroom in
my
house you know so I think my house is
unclean in and of itself but uh again we
in a c to be another we uh we're in
another land we don't govern ourselves
so I don't know if that has anything to
do with the matter or
not but he just answered the question
before what you said read the scripture
again brother that you just
read That's the 19
22 numbers
1922 and whatsoever the unclean person
toucheth shall be unclean and the soul
that toucheth it shall be clean until
evening till the
evening so we come into your house your
house is unclean if you in there you're
unclean until even and that's the end of
it
y all right hope that answered your
question there as we move on to our next
one and let's open the next one up to
the panel also what is it Dev uh yes uh
Zion asked in Matthew
11:1 if being least in the kingom means
Eternal Lake of Fire what does it mean
by he that is least in the kingdom is
greater than John the
Baptist all right Matthew
11 and
um read it brother tenzel and I believe
the guest caller can share some light on
that one go ahead brother we unto you
among them that are born of women there
have not risen a greater than John the
Baptist not withstanding he that is
least in the Kingdom of Heaven is
greater than
he see now we understand that least in
the Kingdom of Heaven is talking about L
of fire but then again too you have
another uh uh uh uh but everybody that's
in God's kingdom is Immortal John is not
Immortal he's Flesh and Blood m
so now how can the Flesh and Blood
person be compared to even the uhh
weakest thing in that's uh
Immortal but in this case then Jesus is
not talking about uh the lake ofi when
he said least in the Kingdom of Heaven
like Solomon said they said he would be
what did he say could be if he could
just be a doorkeeper in the
[Music]
Kingdom all he's saying right here is as
long long as you're Flesh and
Blood you are less than a spiritual
being I don't care what how great you
are among men still you're
mortal but when you're Immortal I
however least you are not talking about
lopi you're greater than John the
Baptist all I have to say yes all right
I'm G leave it right there as we move on
to our next question next one from Malik
secure as in Matthew 12: 31 and 32 could
you give me an example of speaking
against the Holy Ghost and
blasphemy against the Holy
Ghost all right why don't we go there to
that Matthew
12 and ver 31 and 32 31 and 32 go ahead
wherefore I say unto you all manner of
sin and blasphemy shall be forgiven unto
men but the blasphemy against the Holy
Ghost shall not be forgiven unto men and
whosoever speaketh a word against the
son of man it shall be forgiven him
whosoever speaketh against the Holy
Ghost it shall not be forgiven him
neither in this world neither in the
world to come all right so we know that
when you know right and you teach wrong
we know it's no blessing in that open to
the
pound go to Romans the first chapter
start reading in verse
yep for the wrath of God
revealed Romans 1 verse
18 for the wrath of God is revealed from
Heaven against all ungodliness and
unrighteousness of men who hold the
truth and unright
n because that which may be known of God
is manifested in them for God have
showed it unto them for the invisible
thing of him from the creation of the
world are clearly seen being understood
by the things that are made even his
eternal power in Godhead so that they
are without excuse because that when
they knew God they glorify him not as
God neither were thankful but became
vain in their imagination and their
foolish heart was darkened professing
themselves to be wise they became fools
and changed the glory of the
uncorruptible god into the image made
like to uncorruptible men and the to
birds and four-footed beasts and
creeping things wherefore God also gave
them up to uncleanness Du the lust of
their own Hearts to dishonor their own
bodies between themselves who change the
truth of God unto a lie and worship and
serve the creature more than the cre
Creator who is blessed forever amen for
this call God gave them up unto vile
affection for even their women did
change the natural use unto which is
against nature likewise also the men
leaving the natural use of the woman
burnt into their lust one towards
another men with men working that which
is unseemly and receiv receiving in
themselves that recompense of their
error which was meat and even as they
did not like to retain God in their
knowledge God gave them over to a rep
probate mind to do those things which
are not
convenient now that is when you are in
trouble you know the
truth and you understand it deeply
because even said a godhead these are
people with good understanding but still
they teach it wrong and they live wrong
and because they keep teaching it wrong
God turn them over to a reprobate mind
and once you get that reprobate mind it
is over
with Let's Go and show you that what how
what what the uh uh uh uh and what God
do make give you a repated mind let's go
into second Thessalonians the 2
chapter
yeah and these are people that uh uh
that love a lie and they listen to
people that teaches a lie and I show you
what God going to do to them we're going
to Second Thessalonians two and and
we're going to start we're going to read
from one to uh uh
uh four and we're going to
skip now we besee you brotherr by the
coming of our Lord Jesus Christ and by
our gathering together unto him that ye
be not soon Shak admire or be troubled
neither by Spirit nor by word nor by
letter asked from us as that the day of
Christ is at hand let no man deceive you
by any means for that day shall not come
except there come a falling the away
first and that man of sin be revealed
the son of
predition who oppose and exalt himself
above all that is called God or that is
worshiped so that he as God sth in the
temple of God showing himself that he is
God now skip down to verse n this is the
guy these people that uh uh uh that
listen to this and they know that it is
wrong but still they listen go ahead
even him whose coming is after the
working of Satan with all power and
signs and Ling
wonders and with all deceivableness of
unrighteousness in them that perish
because they receive not the love of the
truth that they might be
saved God shall send them strong
delusion that they should believe a lie
that they all might be damned who
believe not the truth but had pleasure
and
unrighteousness now so this talking
about that bad false teaching and people
it is false teaching and they know it's
false
because they know the truth but still
they want to believe a lie so God's
going to send them a strong delusion
that they might believe a lie that they
might be damned that strong
delusion is also called a reprobate mind
that's all I have to say right learn the
truth and walk
therein all right sister Deborah our
next question next question is from Zion
Zion asked in Matthew 4: 5 and 6 when
the devil told Jesus to cast thyself
down was he asking him to bow to him or
to
jump Matthew
4 yes vers five and six all right let's
read five and
six Matthew 4 5 and
six then the devil taketh him up into
the holy C City and sth him on a Pinacle
of the temple and said unto him if thou
be the Son of God cast thyself down for
it is written he shall give his angels
charge concerning thee and in their hand
shall they shall bear thee up lest at
any time thou Dash thaty foot against a
stone and the question
and the question
again uh
is was he uh when the devil told Jesus
to cast thyself down was he asking him
to bow to him or to jump to
jump yeah he was asking asking him to
jump he was he was actually quoting
scripture Psalms 91 so he was asking
Jesus to jump off if you be the Son of
God and the angels don't catch you and
all this kind of stuff he was actually
asking to physically throw yourself off
this
mountain yeah y Luke the 4th chapter
inside
with L
four you start
reading he going Satan going to see a
lot of things toing
and Jesus being full of the Holy Ghost
returned from Jordan and was led by the
spirit Into the Wilderness being 40 days
tempted of the devil and in those days
he did eat nothing and when they were
ended he afterwards hungered and the
devil said unto him if thou be the Son
of God command this stone that it be
made bread and Jesus answered him saying
it is written that man should not live
by bread alone but by every word of God
the devil taking him up into a high
mountain showed unto him all the
kingdoms of the world in a moment of
time and the devil said unto him all
this power will I give Thee the glory of
them for that is delivered unto me and
to whosoever I will I give it if thou
therefore will worship me all shall be
thine now see that he finally got down
to asking Jesus telling Jesus to worship
him look like we said earlier when he
said jump
he meant jump all I have to
say all right hope that answers your
question there sister Deborah next one
next one he also ask what is the mark of
the
beast what is the mark of the beast open
to the
panel we have to wait until we get
there all
right hope that answered your question
next
question yes next one Jennifer Love asks
if our love ones end up in the Lake of
Fire will we be able to recognize
them um yep whatever you look like now
that's that's what you got guest caller
go ahead rich man
Lazarus all you have to go is is is is
see what the the parable that Jesus G
with Lazarus and the rich man they knew
one
another
yeah somebody want to go read it go read
it yeah we gonna read that just in uh
search mode right now we're
going Luke
16 Luke 16 and 19 somewhere in there
Dre
um Luke 16
22 stting in 19
yeah
okay Luke 16 pick it up at 19
corre it was a certain rich man which
was clothed in purple and fine lenen
fair fair sumptuously every day and
there was a certain Begg named Lazarus
which had laid at his gate full of
swords and Desiring to be fed with the
crumbs which failed upon the rich man's
table moreover the dogs came in his
source and it came to pass that the
beggar died and was carried by the
Angels unto Abraham's bosom the rich man
also died and was buried and in hell he
lifted up his eyes being in torment and
see if Abraham are far off and Lazarus
in his bosom and he cried and said
Father Abraham have mercy on me and send
Lazarus that he may dip the tip of his
finger in water and cool my tongue for I
am tormented in this flame but Abraham
said Son remember that thou in thy
lifetime receiveth thaty good things and
likewise Lazarus evil things but now he
is comforted and thou are
tormented besides all this
that's that's enough just let you know
that they recognize one another
yep so you will
recognize y okay you look like is what
you
got all right hope that answered your
question next
question next question D Thornhill says
please explain First Corinthians 11
verse4 should men not wear their hair
long and they want you to uh to and they
ask is there any historical references
showing that Israelite men wore long
hair
Absalon y Absalon had long hair he had
to cut his let's go there let's go to
First Corinthians 11 they asked about
and then we can go to that Absalon if
you got it handy uh brother uh Julius
but let's go to that 1 Corinthians 11
and verse 14 or you might want to go up
higher yeah 14 is good we get straight
to the
point do even not nature teaches you
that if a man have long hair it is a
shame unto
him but if a woman have long hair it is
her glory to her for her hair is given
her for a
covering all right right so did you
locate your scripture there
Julius give me one minute I'm still
looking all right we're in search mode
for that but Sam had long hair didn't
he yeah he did when it got cut he got
weak didn't
he so what about uh
Samson yep that's what uh Tel was just
saying that's a good one de think I want
2 Samuel the 14th
chapter second second Samuel 14 2 Samuel
14 2 Samuel
14 uh I think it was around
six we pick it up at verse
25 25 yeah 2
Samuel uh 14 pick it up around
25 but in all Israel there was none to
be so much praised as abson for his
Beauty from the SES of his foot even to
the crown of his head there was no
blemish in him and when he pulled his
head for it was at every Year's End that
he pulled it because the hair was heavy
on him therefore he pulled it he weighed
the hair of his head at 200 shekels
after the king
way so he he had a lot of
hair
yeah that's right like you said ear
something had long had to to uh when you
say you know that was a statement Paul
made that it's a shame it depends on who
it
is but you don't have no law that said
thou shall have short hair or thou shall
not have long hair
yep and uh Samson's on that same point
when his hair got cut he got weak but
when he grew back he got his strength
back that's correct all right so we're
gonna I'm Gonna Leave it right there and
and move on to the next question uh next
question we can talk right here says I
carry a weapon but I hear people say
they are protected by God am I showing
no faith because I carry to protect
others and
myself opening to the panel it is a law
that you can carry it doesn't say that
if you carried in you don't have uh any
faith Peter had disciples had weapons
Peter had a knife he cut off uh malus's
ear
mhm so and and the Lord he had a sword
and the Lord told him put thy sword back
in thy
sheep all right so we can't say you
don't have faith you know just because
you carry and we can't say because you
don't carry that there's anything wrong
with that either it is a choice that's
left up to that
individual all right I guess we'll move
on to our next question yes moving on S
R funes says when we fast and supplicate
for
guidance when asking God for a sign are
we supposed to ask for a sign that's
within our fast or can it be a sign
after the fast also should we work
during a fast
yeah I know you can work doing a fast
and and uh Dre dealt with something
earlier talking about fasting but let's
open it up to the panel and make sure
it's not the uh the atonement fast
though because you're not to do any work
on that fast that's correct that's
right so um yeah so she want to know are
we supposed to ask for a sign when
you're doing the fast or
uh as for the sign after the
[Music]
fast what did Paul say about people
seeking to have to ass
sign he say evil and adulterous
generation seeketh after a
sign go read
it pa pa tell you a sign is for what
unbelievers somebody go and read that
what that first is it in First
Corinthians
uh let's
see sound like an evil and adulterous
generation Matthew 12 Matthew
12 you can
read while we look at look for the other
ones yeah it's Matthew 16 Ain't It 12
and 39
yeah 38 to uh
40 you want me read that read the
39 then certain of the scribes and other
Pharisees answered crying Master we will
see a sign from thee but he answered and
said unto them and even an adulterous
generation seeketh after a sign and
there should no sign be given to it but
the sign of the Prophet Jonas
and then read that Matthew 16 and4 it's
going to tell you the same
thing a wicked and adulterous generation
seeketh after a sign and there should no
sign be given unto it but the sign of
the Prophet
Jonas your faith should be good enough 1
Corinthians 14 and
22 1 Corinthians
14 and 22
wherefore tongues are for a sign not to
them that believe but to them that
believe not but prophesying serve not
for them that believe not but for them
which
believe so if you praying to prophesying
you make your
request yeah but then you don't ask God
to show you a sign that he going to
Grant your
request go sign for nonbelievers and
even an adulterous generation seek after
toine
what you do is you pray to the Lord and
let him know what you
want it's up to him gred or not but you
know said Give Me A
Sign yeah that's all to say yeah let's
go to Matthew 6 and 6 and once you take
that sign out just do this right here if
you're not asking Matthew 6 and verse 6
one
verse but thou when thou prayest enter
into thy closet and when thou has shut
thy door pray to thy father which is in
secret and thy father which seeth in
secret shall reward the open yep so you
don't have to ask for the sign but
prayer is always in order all right and
Cornell for that for that uh previous
question about uh uh Peter had his sword
you can find that in John St John 18: 10
and
11 all right John 18 vers 10 that was
that was for the person that asked about
carrying a
weapon oh okay
yeah yeah John 18 10 and 11 okay if you
there T shoot it out right
quick then said Jesus unto Peter put up
thy sword unto thy sheath the cup which
my father have given me shall I not
drink
it so he had at verse 10 was talking
about when got his his right ear cut off
right yeah yeah okay thanks for finding
that sister Deborah time check yes the
time is
8:54 uh next question is from
Valencia Valencia asked can you explain
why Jonah was angry and asked the Lord
to take his life and Jonah 4: 1 through3
is
Jonah
4 verses 1 2 and three all right what
don't we go there to that Jonah
for Amos Obadiah and then
Jonah and when you get there brother
tanzel Jona
4 and verse one go
ahead what but it pleased Jonah
exceedingly and he was very angry he
prayed unto the Lord and said I pray
thee Oh Lord was not this my saying when
I was yet in my country so therefore I
fled before unto tarus which I knew that
thou our gracious God and merciful slow
the anger and of great kindness and
repentance thee of the
evil therefore now Lord take I besee
Thee my life for me but it is better for
me to die than to live all right and the
question was why did he say it was
better for him to die than to
live
uh because God spared Nineveh
yesah destroy that's why he didn't want
to prophesy to him because he knew that
they was going to repent that's why he
tried to run away first by a ship got
thrown
overboard yeah so when he went and he
prophesied Nineveh repented from the
King down to the least person and Jonah
didn't like
it yeah to the point you can take my
life because Nineveh did some ugly thing
Nineveh is in the city of Assyria the
Assyrians did some ugly things to
Israel wanted
them they was mad because they
repented yeah okay that's some some good
light there and sister Deborah time is
flying because we having fun next
question yes Comm le as uh cly S
as is job 37 Verse
18 uh in the KJV talking about the
F let's go to Jo
37 and pick it up
that verse
18 37 and 18
uhhuh H has thou with him spread out the
sky which is strong and as a molden
Looking
Glass yep and the sky is part of the
firmament if we take it at what it's
reading there as thou with him spread
out the sky which is strong and as a
molten looking glass sometime you look
up in the sky you can't see one Cloud
you wonder where they all went anybody
else yeah you got something them
versions I think that new world
translations youah Witness Bible they
call it the
expanse yeah but just talking about the
firmament the sky everything above the
ground yeah that's
it okay all right we hope that answers
your question as we come down to our
last question or two next one sister de
yes
um most love as were Peter and Andrew
Gentiles since Jesus chose them when he
was beyond Jordan Galilee of the
Gentiles and Matthew 4 vers 15- 18 is
given again where Peter and Andrew
Gentiles since Jesus chose them when he
was beyond
Jordan okay no no and Julius you dealt
with that a little bit earlier too what
book did they give sister Matthew 4 vers
15-
18 all right so uh brother Julius I look
like you had something to say but go
ahead pick it up at that
15 the land of zabula and the land of
nepalm by the way of the sea Beyond
Jordan Galilee of the
Gentiles it's called the it's called
Galilee of the Gentile because the
Romans was ruling the known world at
that time that's no they were not
Gentiles all of the disciples were Jews
they uh that's why he said Israel only
have I known so it's called Galilee of
the Gentiles because the Gentiles ran
the world at that time the Romans was in
charge and another place it was called
and it was called G the Sea of Galilee
but when the Romans took over it was
called the Sea of
Tiberius because the Romans they not the
emperor Tiberius because the Romans rule
the
world that's right guess
call go and see what Jesus said to his
Apostles CU we talking Apostles here
right
yeah go to Matthew the 10th chapter read
verse one and Skip down and read verses
5 and
six and when he had called unto him his
12 disciples he gave them power against
unclean spirits to cast them out and to
heal all manner of sickness and all
manner of
disease verse
five these 12 Jesus sent forth and
commanded them saying go not into the
way of the Gentiles and to any city of
the Samaritans enter ye not but go
rather to the lost sheep of the House of
Israel if if Peter being a gentile then
the Lord going to tell him not to go in
the way of the Gentile but go to the law
sheep of the House of Israel don't
add this don't make sense
no Romans the 9th chapter verse verse
one start reading at verse one that's
all I have to say after
that Romans
9 and verse
one I say the truth in Christ I lie not
and my conscience also bearing me
witness in the Holy
Ghost that that I have great heaviness
and continual sorrow in my heart but
could wish that myself were a curse from
Christ for my brethren and kid men
according to the flesh who are
Israelites who are
Israelites to whom pertain the adoption
and the glory and the Covenant and the
giving of the law and the service of God
and the
promises so now all that blow on to
Israel y so now if P was Gentile then
they couldn't they couldn't do that
could they
all I have to say all right and that is
a good question to end our session on
sister Deborah time check yes the time
is
9:02 all right we have ran out of time
and if we didn't get to your question we
ask you to not resubmit it sister
Deborah take it put it in rotation and
we will address that question next week
so we want to thank you all from all
around the world who viewed with us this
evening
it was a joy to partake with you and
until we all come together again be safe
be blessed stay prayerful and may the
Lord have mercy on us all as brother
tanzel closes us out Our Father which
are in heaven Hallowed be thy name thy
kingdom come thy will be done in earth
as it is in heaven give us this day our
daily bread and forgive us of our debts
as we forgive our Deb to us
and lead us not into temptation but
Deliver Us from Evil for thine is the
kingdom and the power and the glory
forever in Jesus name we pray amen